steptohealth.com 2017-08-16

# Privacy Policy - Step To Health

The purpose of that which is outlined in the Organic Law 15/1999, December 19th, of Personal Information Protection GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L. with CIF B37527900 informs the user of the existence of personal information files registered in the GRPI (General Registry of Protected Information), to fulfill the legitimate purposes of this entity.

## SENDING AND REGISTRY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Sending personal information is mandatory in order to contact an individual and to receive information regarding products and services offered by said entity. The individual to whom the information belongs declares that he/she is older than 14 years of age.

Refusal to provide the requested personal information, or refusal to accept the present information protection policy will prevent subscription, registration, or the receipt of products and services offered by this entity.

According to the declaration of the Organic Law 15/1999, December 13th, Personal Information Protection, we declare that the personal information which is sent will be incorporated into files pertaining to GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L., address AZAFRANAL 19 2ºA 37001 Salamanca, having implemented all security measures established in Development Regulations in the LOPD, royal decree 1720/2007, December 21st.

## ACCURACY AND VERACITY OF INFORMATION PROVIDED

The user that sends information to GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L. is the sole individual responsible for the veracity, correctness, and appropriateness of the information include, thereby releasing GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L., from any responsibility thereof.

The user guarantees and replies in any case, to the exactness, validity and authenticity of the personal information provides, and promises to maintain the information duly updated.

The user agrees to provide complete and correct information in the registration or subscription format.

GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L. does not respond to the veracity of the information outside of its own making and of that indicated from other sources, and therefore does not assume any responsibility regarding hypothetical losses that could result from the use of said information.

GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L., is exempt from responsibility of any damage or loss that the User could suffer as a consequence of errors, defects or omissions in the information provided to GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L., any time that this information comes from outside sources.

## RELEASE OF INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES

GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L.. will not release user information to third parties. However, in the event that information is released to some other business, express consent by the affected individual will be requested prior to the release.

Exercise of access rights, reformation, cancellation and opposition

Any sort of communication, along with the exercising of access rights, reformation, cancellation and opposition can be directed via mail to: GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L.., AZAFRANAL 19 2ºA 37001 Salamanca, or via email to [info@steptohealth.com](mailto:info@steptohealth.com), with the subject “Information Protection” indicated in the subject line. In order to exercise said rights and by obeying Instruction 1/1998, January 19th, of the Spanish Agency of Information Protection, the user must verify his/her identity to GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L., by sending a photocopy of his/her NATIONAL IDENTITY DOCUMEN or any other valid legal means.

## INFORMATION SECURITY MEASURES

GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L., has adopted the security protection levels of Personal Information that are legally required and listed in RD 1720/2007 of the Development of the LOPD. However, it possesses other additional means, like the latest generation of firewalls, apart from technical measures like encryption software for personal information, restricted users, policies regarding security, users and passwords that expire according to that which is outlined in the LOPD, and other systems designed to prevent misuse, alteration, unauthorized access, and theft of Personal Information provides to GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L..

GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L., will not be responsible for possible damages or losses that could arise out of interference, omissions, interruptions, computer viruses, telephonic breakdowns or disconnections in the operation of this electronic system, caused by outside sources. They are also not responsible for delays or blockages in the present electronic system caused by deficiencies or overloading of the phone lines or the CIP (Center of Information Processing), in the Internet system or other electronic systems, as well as damages that could be caused by third parties through illegal interruptions that are out of the entity’s control.

## ACCEPTANCE AND CONSENT

The user confirms that he/she has been informed of the personal information protection conditions, and has accepted and consented to the treatment thereof on behalf of GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L., in the fashion and for the purposes indicated in this Personal Information Privacy Policy.

GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L. reserves the right to modify this policy to adapt it to new legislature or jurisprudentials as well as the industry’s practices. On said assumption, it provides the policy to adapt to new legislature or jurisprudentials as well as the industry’s practices. On said assumption, GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L. will announce the changes that have been iThe purpose of that which is outlined in the Organic Law 15/1999, December 19th, of Personal Information Protection GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L. with CIF B37527900 informs the user of the existence of personal information files registered in the GRPI (General Registry of Protected Information), to fulfill the legitimate purposes of this entity.

## SENDING AND REGISTRY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Sending personal information is mandatory in order to contact an individual and to receive information regarding products and services offered by said entity. The individual to whom the information belongs declares that he/she is older than 14 years of age.

Refusal to provide the requested personal information, or refusal to accept the present information protection policy will prevent subscription, registration, or the receipt of products and services offered by this entity.

According to the declaration of the Organic Law 15/1999, December 13th, Personal Information Protection, we declare that the personal information which is sent will be incorporated into files pertaining to GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L., address AZAFRANAL 19 2ºA 37001 Salamanca, having implemented all security measures established in Development Regulations in the LOPD, royal decree 1720/2007, December 21st.

## ACCURACY AND VERACITY OF INFORMATION PROVIDED

The user that sends information to GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L. is the sole individual responsible for the veracity, correctness, and appropriateness of the information include, thereby releasing GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L., from any responsibility thereof.

The user guarantees and replies in any case, to the exactness, validity and authenticity of the personal information provides, and promises to maintain the information duly updated.

The user agrees to provide complete and correct information in the registration or subscription format.

GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L. does not respond to the veracity of the information outside of its own making and of that indicated from other sources, and therefore does not assume any responsibility regarding hypothetical losses that could result from the use of said information.

GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L., is exempt from responsibility of any damage or loss that the User could suffer as a consequence of errors, defects or omissions in the information provided to GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L., any time that this information comes from outside sources.

## RELEASE OF INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES

GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L.. will not release user information to third parties. However, in the event that information is released to some other business, express consent by the affected individual will be requested prior to the release.

Exercise of access rights, reformation, cancellation and opposition

Any sort of communication, along with the exercising of access rights, reformation, cancellation and opposition can be directed via mail to: GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L.., AZAFRANAL 19 2ºA 37001 Salamanca, or via email to [info@steptohealth.com](mailto:info@steptohealth.com), with the subject “Information Protection” indicated in the subject line. In order to exercise said rights and by obeying Instruction 1/1998, January 19th, of the Spanish Agency of Information Protection, the user must verify his/her identity to GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L., by sending a photocopy of his/her NATIONAL IDENTITY DOCUMEN or any other valid legal means.

## INFORMATION SECURITY MEASURES

GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L., has adopted the security protection levels of Personal Information that are legally required and listed in RD 1720/2007 of the Development of the LOPD. However, it possesses other additional means, like the latest generation of firewalls, apart from technical measures like encryption software for personal information, restricted users, policies regarding security, users and passwords that expire according to that which is outlined in the LOPD, and other systems designed to prevent misuse, alteration, unauthorized access, and theft of Personal Information provides to GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L..

GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L., will not be responsible for possible damages or losses that could arise out of interference, omissions, interruptions, computer viruses, telephonic breakdowns or disconnections in the operation of this electronic system, caused by outside sources. They are also not responsible for delays or blockages in the present electronic system caused by deficiencies or overloading of the phone lines or the CIP (Center of Information Processing), in the Internet system or other electronic systems, as well as damages that could be caused by third parties through illegal interruptions that are out of the entity’s control.

## ACCEPTANCE AND CONSENT

The user confirms that he/she has been informed of the personal information protection conditions, and has accepted and consented to the treatment thereof on behalf of GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L., in the fashion and for the purposes indicated in this Personal Information Privacy Policy.

GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L. reserves the right to modify this policy to adapt it to new legislature or jurisprudentials as well as the industry’s practices. On said assumption, it provides the policy to adapt to new legislature or jurisprudentials as well as the industry’s practices. On said assumption, GRUPO M CONTIGO S.L. will announce the changes that have been introduced on its webpage with reasonable advance prior to implementation.ntroduced on its webpage with reasonable advance prior to implementation.
